<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Event Engine</title>
    <link>/ee/010_introduction.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Event Engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/ee/010_introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Foreword</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</guid>
      <description>How did we get here? Set the stage for the audience, this page isn&amp;rsquo;t mandatory but will can be a great page for a hook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem Statement</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</guid>
      <description>What is the problem Effective workshops require an important and common problem that the partner&amp;rsquo;s solution will solve. What is the problem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is this partner?</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/14_partner.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/14_partner.html</guid>
      <description>What is HashiCorp? HashiCorp is a remote-first company headquartered in San Francisco that solves development, operations, and security challenges in infrastructure so organizations can focus on business-critical tasks.
HashiCorp was founded by Mitchell Hashimoto and Armon Dadgar in 2012 with the goal of revolutionizing datacenter management: application development, delivery, and maintenance.
The datacenter of today is very different than the datacenter of yesterday, and we think the datacenter of tomorrow is just around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Next Steps</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</guid>
      <description> Workshop Prerequisites There are a few prerequisite tasks you must perform before getting started on this workshop. These are:
 Access to an AWS account w/ proper permissions A Cloud9 IDE Workspace Sign-up for partner&amp;rsquo;s free trial to use solution (if necessary)  In the next section, there will be instructions on how to set everything up, step by step.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
